mygadgetnews.com 2013-05-22

# Privacy Policy & Terms Of Use | MyGadgetNews

MyGadgetNews.com, is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our Web site. You can access MyGadgetNews.com and browse our site without disclosing any personal information. MyGadgetNews.com DOES NOT collect personal information about individuals, such as names, mailing or e-mail addresses, unless it is knowingly provided by the individual and he or she has agreed to the terms under which MyGadgetNews.com will use it.

Third party vendor privacy information:

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on MyGadgetNews.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Disclosure of Information**

MyGadgetNews.com will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We may use IP addresses to compile and provide aggregate statistics about our visitors, traffic patterns, and administer the site. This statistical information may also be related to third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**External Web Sites**

Please note that MyGadgetNews.com contains links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our site that you read the privacy statements of each web site that might collect personally identifying information.

**Terms Of Use**

Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability

BY USING THIS SITE, YOU ASSUME ALL RESPONSIBILITY AND RISK FOR THE USE OF THIS SITE AND THE INTERNET GENERALLY. THE INFORMATION IS PROVIDED “AS IS”, WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. IN NO EVENT SHALL MYGADGETNEWS.COM BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, AND DAMAGES RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS, OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE MATERIALS OR ANY HYPERLINKED SITE, EVEN IF MYGADGETNEWS.COM OR ITS AFFILIATES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

This Site is intended to assist readers by providing news and information on today’s latest technology. MyGadgetNews.com is not responsible for any errors or omissions in the materials or information provided on this Site, any articles or postings for hyperlinks embedded in messages, nor for any loss or damage caused by your reliance on information obtained on this site or in a hyperlinked site.

This site may provide chat rooms, bulletin boards and other means for the public to contribute information and make statements. MyGadgetNews.com does not make any endorsements of these statements nor representations that the statements are true and accurate. MyGadgetNews.com reserves the right to edit statements made within these forums. We also reserve the right to limit or restrict access to users who abuse these forums. You should be cautious when acting on information provided by contributors to these chat rooms. You should not rely solely upon the information and opinions of the chat rooms or bulletin boards.
